Hello Hello friends, you are very welcome to Profit.
Hello friends, we did not add anything else yesterday,
but the next day, trends were going on in our market.
Yesterday, we posted a return from one ID and
today I added some more friends, which was
Ideal and I was asked to fast on Reliance.
Apart from that, I made some strategies
today which the algorithm had subscribed me to
and we will talk about that too. So let's
start the video. First of all, I would like to
talk about IGL or ICL,
friends, and I feel that this series has been falling for a
long time, that is, for the last two-three days,
it has been falling and
its indication is coming very proper
from the algorithm that IGL is worth buying.
Right now, keep the quantity a little low and you
can buy properly from 5 and then you will add
as it becomes stronger
or its hind
questions and that will be the song. So, ideal a
little more, looking at the time of three-four days
or to 9 Kamlesh tender to take profit
and after that we gave the fixed equal trade.  It was
given yesterday, it was called shallow but and before that
we had given HDFC AMC, in both of these
friends, already asked for the algorithm, all
dual falling, send me the timing and
I can see the logic on gas, timing properly
Monday or Tuesday, we can see profit in it,
in such numbers DSC, we can see profit on Monday or Tuesday,
who can't,
something happens on Saturday or Sunday, some different
news comes, the possibility of this is very less, it is
not there in the
chart friends, it
gives us indication of what is going to come, it
gives indication of what is going to happen to Saturn, it gives indication of what is going to come
and there is that
improvement in the logic in the algorithm, it
tells us the details of what is going to come, so it is telling us that the things to come are going to be
seen in the long run, but if we get to
see something soon,
I will tell you immediately by
making a video, then I will tell you about it on Instagram
and if it goes up, then there is profit to be made,
I will also tell you about that  I will give you such numbers and
apart from this, friends, we should do this
for four days, if there is any profit in between, as
we said that we had taken a deficiency,
right, any CMC has already been, it has been quite a
non-profit, I
take it only at the time when I give you the trend and
whoever has taken it, they must have already made profit
many times but did not do it
because they are trying to get more
profit and whatever little activation they could get, their
intensity of profit could not be swayed, that is
why we did not do it, it has just gone down
and now it is starting to come back, so it is good, we will have
good confidence on the algorithm,
only this is going to go off, ideally
we will get three to four days, in that
you can get profit in between, you get it,
book it,
what is the profit for us, friends, if we
get 0.5 percent profit in the day, then also
how much is it for the month, you can see
how much FD gives you, 6.7 percent, right now it has become even
less than that, so  We are getting more than that, there is
no need to search for it and the Gori Dam
which gives us the indication that
we are getting so much security
that it is going to be a little upset and if there is a
little, we will take a little from it,
keep such a reminder, keep trailing it by keeping a stop loss, so it got a
little late
but what I
meant to say in this was that then I told you that you have to
watch on Bike F4 Reliance, you have to
watch on Reliance, so the algorithm on Reliance had already
come in the watch list yesterday afternoon, one
was Muthoot Finance and the other was Reliance,
both of which were there but I had not told you
because if you look at Muthoot Finance, then
we had seen a very big channel in the country about
volume on the off side and my coding of volume,
I said some coding is going on, so the
coding of volume is going on in it right now
and I was not that computer in it
but that was a
very big candle of volume, that is why I did not ask you to
talk to it or I did
not ask Muthoot Finance to share it, but today the
algorithm had also asked you to save it in the
morning and the portrait  I had taken it but did
not tell you because until I
am not confident, I have
not completed the coding, if there is no complaint in it then
I will not tell you, so I did
not tell you because it was 1217, 1270, then
we got an indication from the algorithm that this
bike is too late
and after that see, it went up to 1118,
that strong, fantastic and we are
seeing sim-sim of Reliance on Monday or Tuesday,
like Muthoot Finance, and the algorithm has
asked us to keep it in the watch list, Monday will
confirm whether we will be trailing in it or not,
so Dashrath, thank you so much friends and
we talked to the Chairman and CEO of IGL about
Lamhat and all four of Reliance, from
such number updates we
will wait in C and on Monday-Tuesday we may get profit,
then and affair in Reliance, we have to
set the market as to what is the situation
in Reliance and IGL, we will have it by Thursday
How can the problem be given profit at any time? Thank you so much friends, if you are liking it, are getting
profit, you like low risk
investment or
examination, then
share it with your friends, share this channel with your friends,
follow Stratus on Instagram and
give me some encouragement too, I do not believe that I am such a
big artist or have such a big list,
but whatever is my understanding,
whatever is my engineering college,
I try my best to apply to that many
and if I get your love, we will
go a long way Da Recipes Thank you so much friends
by A